Guide to the Palladium Flyers Collection MSS 441
Fales Library and Special Collections
- OVERSIZE Series VI: Musical Performances
  - Godfathers [You Won't Pay, You Will Dance]: Live at Palladium, October 16 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Live in Concert: The Smithereens at Palladium, December 17 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- OVERSIZE Series VII: Parties
  - Details: Third Birthday At The Palladium, June 19, 1985 (Map-case 2D, Folder 1)
  - The 60's, July 25, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 9)